Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 18, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Equal Employment Opportunity Training: A Program for Affirmative Action, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Author: U.S. Department of the Army
  - Item 5: Fear Frustration Backlash: The New Crisis in Civil Rights, Publication (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Author: Bayard Rustin
  - Item 6: A Memorandum to Municipalities: Guidelines for Municipal Human Relations Committees, Publication (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Author: The National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials
- Box: 18, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Discrimination in Apartment Buildings, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 23)
    Author: Daniel G. Hill
- Box: 18, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Settlement of Case of Apartment Discrimination in Windsor, Ontario, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Author: The Ontario Human Rights Commission
    Notes: March 7, 1963
  - Item 2: Settlement of the Case of Twin Gables Beach, Discriminatory Sign, Windsor, Ontario, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: July 12, 1963
  - Item 3: Board of Inquiry into Discrimination at Mitchell's Bay Sportsman Camp, Chatham, Ontario, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: July 31, 1963
  - Item 4: Settlement of Case of Discrimination in a Windsor Beauty Salon, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 10, 1963
  - Item 5: Settlement of Case of Discrimination at el Mocambo Dance Club, Toronto, Ontario, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: August 1, 1963
  - Item 6: Settlement of Case of Barber Shop Discrimination in Windsor, Ontario, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: October 9, 1963
  - Item 7: Settlement of the Case Involving Employment Application Forms Used by the City of Ottawa, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: February 26, 1964
  - Item 8: Settlement of Case Involving Sarnia Area Cottage Rental, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Notes: May 29, 1964
- Box: 18, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: In Search of Housing, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Box: 18, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Equality of Opportunity in College Admissions, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Religion and Race: Barriers to College?, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Author: A.C. Ivy and Irwin Ross
  - Item 3: Text of The Supreme Court Decision on Segregation in Public Schools, 1954; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Author: New Jersey Department of Education
  - Item 4: Brown v. Board of Education, 1953; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Author: Supreme Court of the United States
    Notes: October 1953
  - Item 5: College Admission Practices with Respect to Race, Religion and National Origin of Connecticut High School Graduates, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Author: Henry G. Stetler
  - Item 6: The State of the Community, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Notes: Summer, 1949
  - Item 7: How Can We Fight Discrimination in Higher Education, 1946; Publication (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Author: Queens College
    Notes: April 2, 1946
- Box: 18, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Statement of the New York City Special Committee on Racial and Religious Prejudice, Publication (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Author: New York City Special Committee on Racial and Religious Prejudice
  - Item 2: Toward Quality Secondary Education, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Author: New York City Public Schools
- Box: 18, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Racial Imbalance in the Public Schools: The Current Status of Federal and New York Law, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 28)
    Author: New York State Bar Association
    Notes: October 20, 1964
- Box: 18, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights U.S.A.: Public Schools; Cities in the North and West, 1963: Buffalo, Publication (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: Los Angeles City Schools, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Box: 18, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Dixie Teachers Report Their Pupils Learn Well in Mixed-Race Schools, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Author: Wall Street Journal
    Notes: January 20, 1964
  - Item 2: American Education and the Search for Equal Opportunity, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Author: Educational Policies Commission
  - Item 3: School Segregation, Northern Style, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Author: Will Maslow & Richard Cohen
  - Item 4: The Disadvantaged Poor: Education and Employment; Summary of Recommendations, 1966; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Equality of Educational Opportunity, 1966; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: The Urban School Crisis; An Anthology of Essays, 1966; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Author: League for Industrial Democracy
  - Item 7: Integrated School Books, 1967; Publication (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Author: NAACP Education Department
- Box: 18, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Statistical Data on Negro Enrollment in All-Negro Schools, Publication (Box 18, Folder 31)
    Author: West Virginia Human Rights Commission
- Box: 18, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: FEPC Reference Manual, 1948; Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: National Community Relations Advisory Council
  - Item 2: Fair Employment Practice Act, Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Equal Employment Opportunity through Affirmitive Action, 1966; Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: Archdiocese of Seattle
  - Item 4: Fair Employment Practices Legislation is a Critical Issue Throughout the Country, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: American Council on Race Relations
    Notes: March 14, 1949
  - Item 5: Abolition of Economic and Social Discriminatory Measures Against Workers, Based on Race or Colour, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: United Nations Economic and Social Council
    Notes: December 21, 1949
  - Item 6: The Work of Jewish Agencies in the Field of Employment Discrimination, Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Item 7: Employing Minorities Successfully, Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: American Friends Service Committee
  - Item 8: A Cooperative Employment Practices Plan for Your Business, 1949; Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: Cleveland Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 9: Nor Can Government, 1948; Publication (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Author: Donald R. Richberg
    Notes: Winter 1948
- Box: 18, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Infringements of Trade Union Rights in South Africa, 1969; Publication (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Declaration Concerning the Policy of "Apartheid" of the Republic of South Africa, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: The Struggle Against Discrimination, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 33)
    Author: A.M. Said Salama
  - Item 4: Work Reservation, Its Background, Motivation and Application to the Benefit of All Racial Groups in South Africa, Publication (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Box: 18, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Equal Employment Opportunity Seminar, 1967; Publication (Box 18, Folder 34)
    Author: Alaska State Commission for Human Rights
    Notes: March 15 & 16, 1967
- Box: 18, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Report to Governor Edmund G. Brown; Second Ethnic Survey of Employment and Promotion in State Government, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Age Discrimination in Public Agencies, 1966; Publication (Box 18, Folder 35)
    Author: California Citizens' Advisory Committee on Aging
  - Item 3: Promoting Equal Job Opportunity, Publication (Box 18, Folder 35)
    Author: California Fair Employment Practice Commission
  - Item 4: California Fair Employment Practice Act, Publication (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Item 5: Official Notice to All California Employers, Publication (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Box: 18, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Discrimination in Employment, 1970; Publication (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: The Age Discrimination Act, 1966; Publication (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Protection Under Law Against Employment Discrimination, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: The Ontario Human Rights Code, 1961-62, 1965; Publication (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Declaration of Equal Employment Opportunity, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 36)
    Notes: March 24, 1964
- Box: 18, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Discrimination in Employment, 1963; Publication (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Box: 18, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Towards Racial Understanding, Publication (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Box: 18, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Settlement of Two Cases of Employment Discrimination in Ottawa, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 39)
    Notes: July 30, 1964
  - Item 2: Settlement of a Case of Employment Discrimination on the Part of Florida Men Attending a Convention in Toronto, 1964; Publication (Box 18, Folder 39)
    Notes: June 5, 1964
- Box: 18, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Antidiscrimination Provisions in Major Contracts, 1961; Publication (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Box: 18, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Laws Against Discrimination, Publication (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Author: Connecticut Inter-Racial Commission
  - Item 2: A Brief Description of the Connecticut Fair Employment Practices Act, Publication (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Author: Connecticut Inter- Racial Commission
  - Item 3: What Does the F.E.P.A. Mean to You?, Publication (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: The Connecticut Fair Employment Act, Publication (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Item 5: An Act Concerning Fair Employment Practices, Publication (Box 18, Folder 41)
    Author: Connecticut Senate
- Box: 18, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Uber die Unmoglichkeit eines Grundsatzes der Gleichbehandlung im Arbeitsrecht, 1968; Publication (Box 18, Folder 42)
    Author: N.G. Elwert Verlag Marburg
- Box: 18, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Employment of Coloured Workersin the Birmingham Area, Publication (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Author: Leslie Stephens
  - Item 2: Race Relations and the Engineering Industry, Publication (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Author: Ivan Hattingh
  - Item 3: Monty Meth, Publication (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Author: Here to Stay
  - Item 4: A Race Relations Audit, 1971; Publication (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Author: Runnymede Trust
    Notes: February 1971
  - Item 5: Union Policy and Workplace Practice: A Black Worker Alleges Discrimination, 1970; Publication (Box 18, Folder 43)
    Author: Robert M. Harrison
- Box: 19, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Questioning Applicants for Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Box: 19, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Kentucky School Pairing Plans, 1967; Publication (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Box: 19, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report on Maryland: Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Author: Maryland Advisory Committee to the United States Commission on Civil Rights
  - Item 2: Racial Discrimination in Maryland's Employment Agency, 1969; Publication (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Author: State of Maryland Commission on Human Relations
    Notes: June 25, 1969
- Box: 19, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 1964: Findings, Publication (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Author: Wisconsin Industrial Commission
- Box: 19, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: What FEPC Means to You, Publication (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Author: City of Minneapolis Fair Employment Commission
- Box: 19, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How Valid are the Arguments Againsty Fair Employment Legislation?, 1952; Publication (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Author: League of Women Voters of Minnesota
    Notes: September 1952
- Box: 19, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Survey of Missouri and Federal Laws Relating to Discrimination in Employment Because of Sex, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Author: Missouri Commission on Human Rights
    Notes: March 18, 1966
- Box: 19, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report of the Nebraska Legislative Council Committee on Hiring Practices, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Box: 19, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Primer for the Public on the New Jersey Law Against Discrimination, Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: The Anti-Discrimination Law of 1945, 1949; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Report on a Survey of Employment Policies and Practices Involving Minority Groups in Bergen County New Jersey, 1952; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Report of a Preliminary Study of Employment Practices Involving Minority Group Workers, 1949; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Notes: February 19, 1949
  - Item 5: Report of a Preliminary Study of Employment Practices Involving Minority Group Workers, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 23, 1948
  - Item 6: Report of a Preliminary Study of Employment Practices Involving Minority Group Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Notes: October 20, 1947
  - Item 7: Report of the New Jersey Minorities Project, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Notes: 1945-1948
  - Item 8: Survey of Equal Employment Opportunities in New Jersey Investor-Owned Public Utilities, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Author: Myron J. Levin
- Box: 19, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Mutual Savings Banks of New York City, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Author: American Jewish Committee
  - Item 2: Summary Report and Selected Materials from the Record of the Hearings on Employment Patterns, Policies and Practices in the Theatre Industry and the Motion Picture Industry, Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Author: Nelson A. Rockefeller
  - Item 3: White Collar Employment in 100 Major New York City Corporations, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Author: U.S. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission
  - Item 4: White Collar Employment in the New York City Financial Community, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Bias in the Building Industry, 1967; Publication (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Author: City of New York Commission on Human Rights
    Notes: 1963-1967
- Box: 19, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Inside Facts: The Law Against Discrimination, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: An Equal Chance to Get the Job, to Keep the Job, to Grow on the Job, Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Report of the Governor's Committee on Employment of Minority Groups in the News Media, 1969; Publication (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Box: 19, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Regional Hearings on Apprenticeship Standards, Affirmitive Action, Testing, Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Author: New York State Division of Human Rights
  - Item 2: Equal Opportunities for Men and Women in New York State: A Review of the Complaint Record, 1969; Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Notes: 1965-1969
  - Item 3: Minority Manpower Statistics, 1971; Publication (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Notes: July 1971
- Box: 19, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The North Carolina Good Neighbor Program, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Author: North Carolina Good Neighbor Council
- Box: 19, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Discrimination in the Building Trades, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: New York State Advisory Committee
  - Item 2: Report, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: Building Industry of New York City Referral Committee
    Notes: December 19, 1963
  - Item 3: The Boston Drama, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: Urban League of Greater Boston
  - Item 4: Toward Democracy in Government, 1949; Publication (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Author: City of Cambridge Civic Unity Committee
    Notes: May 5, 1949
- Box: 19, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Fair Employment Practice Commission, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Author: City of Philadelphia
    Notes: March 12, 1948
  - Item 2: Fair Employment Practice Ordinance, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Employing 'Minorities' Successfully, Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: City of Philadelphia Fair Employment Practice Ordinance, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Author: City of Philadelphia Fair Employment Practice Commission
- Box: 19, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Policies of Commission, Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Author: Rhode Island Commission for Fair Employment Practices
  - Item 2: Rules of Practice and Procedure, 1949; Publication (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Box: 19, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Report, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Author: Northern Rhodesia
- Box: 19, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Workers and Trade Unions Against Apartheid, Publication (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Author: World Federation of Trade Unions
- Box: 19, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Unfinished Business: A Fair Employment Handbook, Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Author: Metropolitan Detroit Council on Fair Employment Practice
  - Item 2: The Controversy Over Equal Rights for Negroes, 1956; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Color Line in Industry, 1944; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Notes: April 1944
  - Item 4: Discrimination in Employment, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Author: R.K. McNickle
    Notes: December 17, 1948
  - Item 5: Prohibiting Discrimination in Employment Because of Race, Religion, Color, National Origin, or Ancestry, 1948; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Notes: March 2, 1948
  - Item 6: National Act Against Discrimination in Employment, 1950; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Notes: May 5, 1950
  - Item 7: The Fair Employment Practice Act, 1945; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Notes: February 20, 1945
  - Item 8: Employment of Minority Group Members in 115 Large American Public Libraries, 1953; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Author: Kent State University
    Notes: July 13-31, 1953
  - Item 9: Your Rights Under State and Local Fair Employment Practice Laws, 1955; Publication (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Notes: November 1955
- Box: 19, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Age Discrimination in Employment Act of 1967, Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Author: Commerce Clearing House, Inc.
  - Item 2: Bias in the Building Industry, 1967; Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: The American Dream: Equal Opportunity, 1962; Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Author: President's Committee on Equal Employment Opportunity
    Notes: May 19, 1962
  - Item 4: Christian Influence Toward the Development and Use of All Labor Resources Without Regard to Race, Color, Religion, or National Origin, 1960; Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Notes: December 9, 1960
  - Item 5: Break Down Your Employment Barriers, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 20)
    Author: Theodore V. Purcell
    Notes: July-August 1968
- Box: 19, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Employer's Guide to Equal Opportunity, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: George Schermer
  - Item 2: The High Cost of Discrimination, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: Elmo Roper
  - Item 3: How Race Relations Affect Your Business, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: Theodore W. Kheel
  - Item 4: Equal Opportunity in FAA Employment, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Federal Aviation Administration
    Notes: December 12, 1968
  - Item 5: Equal Employment Opportunities, 1967; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: American Bankers Association
    Notes: September 26, 1967
  - Item 6: Equal Employment Opportunities, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: Dartnell Corporation
  - Item 7: Equal Employment Opportunity Affirmative Action Plan, 1976; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Equality of Opportunity in Manpower Programs, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Job Discrimination is Illegal, 1967; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: Sharon Leventhal
  - Item 10: Denominational Statements with Reference to Feir Employment Practices, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: National Council of the Churches of Christ in USA
  - Item 11: Fair Employment Practices, 1970; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Notes: February 6, 1970
  - Item 12: Fair Employment Practices, 1970; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: Laws on Sex Discrimination in Employment, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Notes: November 1, 1965
  - Item 14: Equal Employment Opportunities for Women, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Women's Bureau
    Notes: October 1, 1965
  - Item 15: Equal Opportunity is Good Labor Practice, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: National Conference of Christians and Jews
  - Item 16: Know Your Employment Rights, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 17: General Provisions, 1961; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. General Services Administration
    Notes: April 1961
  - Item 18: The High Cost of Discrimination, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 19: A Current Look At: The Negro & Title VII, Sex and Title VII, 1967; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 20: Equal Employment Opportunities Enforcement Act, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Notes: May 8, 1968
  - Item 21: Equal Employment Opportunity Under Federal Law, 1966; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 22: Help Wanted; Or is it?, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 23: Rulings on Pre-Employment Inquiries, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 24: Guide to Equal Pay Act, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 25: Equal Opportunity in Employment, Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 26: Equal Employment Opportunity Under Federal and State Laws, 1970; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: Joseph E. Champagne & Gary D. Duncan
  - Item 27: How Race Relations Affect Your Business, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 28: The Equal Employment Opportunity Law, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Item 29: Equal Employment Opportunity in the Defense Supply Agency, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Author: U.S. Defense Supply Agency
- Box: 19, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Negro Drive for Job Equality, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Item 2: The New Age Discrimination Law -- How it Affects Your Employment Practices, 1968; Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Author: Prentice-Hall, Inc.
    Notes: June 4, 1968
  - Item 3: Looking Ahead -- Title VII: Equal Employment Opportunity, 1965; Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Author: Mary Dublin Keyserling
    Notes: April 5, 1965
  - Item 4: Report on Department of Defense Use of Contractor, Potomac Institute, Inc. to Study Equal Employment Opportunities in the Military Services, 1964; Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Notes: April 9, 1964
  - Item 5: The Negro Drive for Job Equality, 1963; Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Item 6: The New Civil Rights Law and Your Business, Publication (Box 19, Folder 22)